Preliminary Guide to the Graduate Student Enrollment Management Office records, 1978-2009 RG0136
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
Graduate Student Enrollment Management records
1978-2009
1990-2007
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
George Washington University. Graduate Studies and Academic Affairs. Graduate Student Enrollment Management
RG0136
4 Linear Feet 4 record cartons
The Office of Graduate Student Enrollment Management falls under the Office of Graduate Studies and Academic Affairs. This collection contains reports, programs, registration forms, budgets, minutes, evaluations, publications, attendance statistics, videos, and banners related to the Graduate and Professional School Fair. Materials date from 1978 to 2009, with the bulk of the material falling between 1990 and 2007.
Conditions Governing Access
This collection is open for research.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Transferred by the Office of Graduate Student Enrollment Management, 08/06/2009 (2009.045).
Arrangement
Organized into 1 series: Graduate and Professional School Fair
Scope and Contents
The records of the Graduate Student Enrollment Office contain reports, programs, registration forms, budgets, minutes, evaluations, publications, attendance statistics, videos, and banners all related to the Graduate and Professional School Fair. Materials date from 1978 to 2009, with the bulk of the material falling between 1990 and 2007.
Biographical / Historical
The Office of Graduate Student Enrollment Management falls under the Office of Graduate and Special Enrollment Management, the Office of Graduate Studies and Academic Affairs, and finally the Executive Vice President for Academic Affairs.
Graduate and Professional School Fair; Universities and colleges -- Graduate work -- Admission; Universities and colleges -- Graduate work; Universities and colleges -- Graduate work -- Administration; George Washington University
- Graduate and Professional School Fair, 1978-2009; 1990-2007; Series 1; George Washington University. Graduate Studies and Academic Affairs. Graduate Student Enrollment Management; 6 Linear Feet 4 record cartons (Box 1, Box 2, Box 3, Box 4)
  Scope and Contents
  This series contains material pertaining to the planning and implementation of the Graduate and Professional School Fair. Types of material include programs, reports, registration forms, budges, evaluations, minutes, publications ("Roll Call" Graduate and Law Schools Guide"), attendance statistics, videotapes, and banners.
  Arrangement
  Arranged by topic, then chronologically. Materials are in the order in which they were sent to the University Archives by the Graduate Student Enrollment Management office.
  Graduate and Professional School Fair
  - 2005 GPSF Law Day Registrations A-Q, 01/01/2005-12/31/2005; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - 2005 GPSF Law Day Registrations R-Z, 01/01/2005-12/31/2005; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - 2006 GPSF Law Day Registrations A-R, 01/01/2006-12/31/2006; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - 2006 GPSF Law Day Registrations S-Z, 01/01/2006-12/31/2006; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - 2007 GPSF Law Day Registrations A-R, 01/01/2007-12/31/2007; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - 2007 GPSF Law Day Registrations S-Z, 01/01/2007-12/31/2007; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - 2005 GPSF Grad Day Registrations A-G, 01/01/2005-12/31/2005; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - 2005 GPSF Grad Day Registrations H-S, 01/01/2005-12/31/2005; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - 2005 GPSF Grad Day Registrations T-Z, 01/01/2005-12/31/2005; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - 2006 GPSF Grad Day Registrations A-G, 01/01/2006-12/31/2006; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - 2006 GPSF Grad Day Registrations H-R, 01/01/2006-12/31/2006; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - 2006 GPSF Grad Day Registrations S-U, 01/01/2006-12/31/2006; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - 2006 GPSF Grad Day Registrations U-Z, 01/01/2006-12/31/2006; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - 2007 GPSF Grad Day Registrations A-G, 01/01/2007-12/31/2007; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - 2007 GPSF Grad Day Registrations H-T, 01/01/2007-12/31/2007; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - 2007 GPSF Grad Day Registrations U-Z, 01/01/2007-12/31/2007; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Grad Fair Financials 1998-1999, 6/1/1998-7/31/1999; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Grad Fair Financials 1999-2000, 7/1/1999-6/30/2000; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Grad Fair Financials 2000-2001 (1 of 2), 7/1/2000-12/31/2000; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Grad Fair Financials 2000-2001 (2 of 2), 1/1/2001-6/30/2001; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Grad Fair Financials 2001-2002 (1 of 3), 7/1/2001-10/30/2001; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Grad Fair Financials 2001-2002 (2 of 3), 10/1/2001-12/31/2001; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Grad Fair Financials 2001-2002 (3 of 3), 1/1/2002-6/30/2002; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Grad Fair Financials 2002-2003 (1 of 2), 7/1/2002-10/31/2002; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Grad Fair Financials 2002-2003 (2 of 2), 11/1/2002-6/30/2003; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Grad Fair Financials 2003-2004 (1 of 2), 7/1/2003-9/30/2003; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Grad Fair Financials 2003-2004 (2 of 2), 10/01/2003-6/30/2004; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Grad Fair Financials 2004-2005 (1 of 2), 7/1/2004-12/31/2004; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Grad Fair Financials 2004-2005 (2 of 2), 01/01/2005-06/30/2005; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Grad Fair Financials 2005-2006 (1 of 2), 7/1/2005-10/31/2005; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Grad Fair Financials 2005-2006 (2 of 2), 11/1/2005-6/30/2006; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Grad Fair Financials 2006-2007 (1 of 2), 7/1/2006-10/30/2006; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Grad Fair Financials 2006-2007 (2 of 2), 10/1/2006-12/31/2006; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Grad Fair Financials 2007-2008 (1 of 2), 1/1/2007-8/31/2007; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Grad Fair Financials 2007-2008 (2 of 2), 9/1/2007-6/30/2008; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Grad Fair Financials 2008-2009, 07/01/2008-02/28/2009; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - GPSF Committee- 1980, 01/01/1980-12/31/1980; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - GPSF Committee- 1981, 01/01/1981-12/31/1981; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - GPSF Committee- 1988, 01/01/1988-12/31/1988; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - GPSF Committee- 1989, 01/01/1989-12/31/1989; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - GPSF Committee- 1990, 1/1/1990-12/31/1990; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - GPSF Committee- 1991, 01/01/1991-12/31/1991; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - GPSF Committee- 1992, 01/01/1992-12/31/1992; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - GPSF Committee- 1993, 1/1/1993-12/31/1993; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - GPSF Committee- 1994, 01/01/1994-12/31/1994; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - GPSF Committee- 1995, 01/01/1995-12/31/1995; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - GPSF Committee- 1996, 01/01/1996-12/31/1996; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - GPSF Committee- 1997, 01/01/1997-12/31/1997; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - GPSF Committee- 1998, 1/1/1998-12/31/1998; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - GPSF Committee- 1999, 01/01/1999-12/31/1999; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - GPSF Committee- 2000, 01/01/2000-12/31/2000; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - GPSF Committee- 2001, 01/01/2001-12/31/2001; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - GPSF Committee- 2002, 01/01/2002-12/31/2002; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - GPSF Committee- 2003, 01/01/2003-12/31/2003; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - GPSF Committee- 2004, 01/01/2004-12/31/2004; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - GPSF Committee- 2005, 01/01/2005-12/31/2005; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - GPSF Committee- 2006, 01/01/2006-12/31/2006; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - GPSF Committee- 2007, 01/01/2007-12/31/2007; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - GPSF - Vendor/I-9 Requests, undated; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Logos, undated; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Representative Evaluations, 1/1/1998-10/30/2006; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Roll Call 2004, 1/1/2004-12/31/2004; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Roll Call 2005, 1/1/2005-12/31/2005; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Roll Call 2006, 1/1/2006-12/31/2006; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Roll Call 2007, 1/1/2007-12/31/2007; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Roll Call 2008, 1/1/2008-12/31/2008; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Panels 1998, 1/1/1998-12/31/1998; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Panels 2001, 1/1/2001-12/31/2001; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Panels 2003, 1/1/2003-12/31/2001; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Panels 2004, 1/1/2004-12/31/2004; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Panels 2005, 1/1/2005-12/31/2005; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Panels 2006, 1/1/2006-12/31/2006; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - 1978-1992 Statistics Summary, 1/1/1978-12/31/1992; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - 1989 Statistics, 1/1/1989-12/31/1989; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - 1990 Statistics, 1/1/1990-12/31/1990; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - 1991 Statistics, 1/1/1991-12/31/1991; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - 1992 Statistics, 1/1/1992-12/31/1992; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - 1993 Statistics, 1/1/1993-12/31/1993; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - 1993-1994 Statistics, 1/1/1993-12/31/1994; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - 1995 Statistics, 1/1/1995-12/31/1995; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - 1996 Statistics, 1/1/1996-12/31/1996; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - 1997 Statistics, 1/1/1997-12/31/1997; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - 1998 Statistics, 1/1/1998-12/31/1998; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - 1999 Statistics, 1/1/1999-12/31/1999; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - 2000 Statistics, 1/1/2000-12/31/2000; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - 2001 Statistics, 1/1/2001-12/31/2001; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - 2002 Statistics, 1/1/2002-12/31/2002; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - 2003 Statistics, 1/1/2003-12/31/2003; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - 2005 Statistics, 1/1/2005-12/31/2005; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - 2006 Statistics, 1/1/2006-12/31/2006; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - 2007 Statistics, 1/1/2007-12/31/2007; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - 2008 Statistics, 1/1/2008-12/31/2008; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Program 1978, 1/1/1978-12/31/1978; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Program 1979, 1/1/1979-12/31/1979; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Program 1980, 1/1/1980-12/31/1980; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Program 1981, 1/1/1981-12/31/1981; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Program 1982, 1/1/1982-12/31/1982; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Program 1983, 1/1/1983-12/31/1983; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - Program 1984, 1/1/1984-12/31/1984; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - Program1990, 1/1/1990-12/31/1990; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - Program 1992, 1/1/1992-12/31/1992; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - Program 1993, 1/1/1993-12/31/1993; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - Program 1994, 1/1/1994-12/31/1994; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - Program 1995, 1/1/1995-12/31/1995; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - Program 1996, 1/1/1996-12/31/1996; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 44)
  - Program 1997, 1/1/1997-12/31/1997; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 45)
  - Program 1998, 1/1/1998-12/31/1998; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 46)
  - Program 1999, 1/1/1999-12/31/1999; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 47)
  - Program 2000, 1/1/2000-12/31/2000; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 48)
  - Program 2001, 1/1/2001-12/31/2001; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 49)
  - Program 2002, 1/1/2002-12/31/2002; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 50)
  - Program 2003, 1/1/2003-12/31/2003; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 51)
  - Program 2004, 1/1/2005-12/31/2005; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 52)
  - Program 2005, 1/1/2006-12/31/2006; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 53)
  - Program 2006, 1/1/2006-12/31/2006; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 54)
  - Program 2007, 1/1/2007-12/31/2007; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 55)
  - Program 2008, 1/1/2008-12/31/2008; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 56)
  - GPSF Banner, undated; Series 1 (Box 3, Object 1)
  - GPSF Banner, undated; Series 1 (Box 3, Object 2)
  - BetacamSP Videotape - GW Television - Graduate and Professional School Fair (Tape 1 of 3), 9/28/1998-9/28/1998; Series 1 (Box 4, Videocassette 1)
  - BetacamSP Videotape - GW Television - Graduate and Professional School Fair (Tape 2 of 3), 9/28/1998-9/28/1998; Series 1 (Box 4, Videocassette 2)
  - BetacamSP Videotape - GW Television - Graduate and Professional School Fair (Tape 3 of 3), 9/28/1998-9/28/1998; Series 1 (Box 4, Videocassette 3)
  - BetacamSP Videotape - GW Television - Graduate and Professional School Fair (Tape 1 of 2), 9/28/1998-9/28/1998; Series 1 (Box 4, Videocassette 4)
  - BetacamSP Videotape - GW Television - Graduate and Professional School Fair (Tape 2 or 2), 9/28/1998-9/28/1998; Series 1 (Box 4, Videocassette 5)
  - BetacamSP Videotape - GW Television - Graduate and Professional School Fair (Tape 1 of 2), 9/29/1998-9/28/1998; Series 1 (Box 4, Videocassette 6)
  - BetacamSP Videotape - GW Television - Graduate and Professional School Fair (Tape 2 of 2), 9/29/1998-9/29/1998; Series 1 (Box 4, Videocassette 7)
  - BetacamSP Videotape - GW Television - Graduate and Professional School Fair (Tape 1 of 2), 9/29/1998-9/28/1999; Series 1 (Box 4, Videocassette 8)
  - BetacamSP Videotape - GW Television - Graduate and Professional School Fair (Tape 2 of 2), 9/29/1998-9/29/1999; Series 1 (Box 4, Videocassette 9)
  - BetacamSP Videotape- Graduate and Professional School Fair - How to Take the GRE, 9/27/1999-9/27/1999; Series 1 (Box 4, Videocassette 10)
  - BetacamSP Videotape - Graduate and Professional School Fair - How to Apply to Graduate School, 9/27/1999-9/27/1999; Series 1 (Box 4, Videocassette 11)
  - BetacamSP Videotape- Graduate and Professional School Fair - How to Apply to Graduate School, 9/28/1999-9/28/1999; Series 1 (Box 4, Videocassette 12)
  - BetacamSP Videotape - Graduate and Professional School Fair - How to Take the LSAT, 9/28/1999-9/28/1999; Series 1 (Box 4, Videocassette 13)
  - VHS Videotape - Graduate & Professional School Fair - "How to Apply to Graduate School", 9/27/1999-9/27/1999; Series 1 (Box 4, Videocassette 14)
  - VHS Videotape - Graduate & Professional School Fair - "How to Take the GRE", 9/27/1999-9/27/1999; Series 1 (Box 4, Videocassette 15)
  - VHS Videotape - Graduate & Professional School Fair - "How to Take the LSAT", 9/28/1999-9/28/1999; Series 1 (Box 4, Videocassette 16)
  - VHS Videotape - Graduate & Professional Fair - "How to Apply to Law School", 9/28/1999-9/28/1999; Series 1 (Box 4, Videocassette 17)
  - VHS Videotape - GW Television - Graduate & Professional School Fair - Panel Discussions - LSAT Strategy Session, undated; Series 1 (Box 4, Videocassette 18)
  - VHS Videotape - GW Television - Graduate & Professional School Fair - Panel Discussions - Computerized Testing: Understanding the GRE & GMAT, undated; Series 1 (Box 4, Videocassette 19)
  - VHS Videotape - Capital Television, Inc. - GPSF - How to Apply to Graduate Study, 1/1/1993-12/31/1993; Series 1 (Box 4, Videocassette 20)
  - VHS Videotape - Capital Television, Inc. - GPSF - How to Apply to Law School, 1/1/1993-12/31/1993; Series 1 (Box 4, Videocassette 21)
  - VHS Videotape - Capital Television, Inc. - GPSF - Getting Through Law School, 1/1/1994-12/31/1994; Series 1 (Box 4, Videocassette 22)
  - VHS Videotape - Capital Television, Inc. - GPSF - Applying to & Financing Law School, 1/1/1994-12/31/1994; Series 1 (Box 4, Videocassette 23)
  - VHS Videotape - Capital Television, Inc. - GPSF - Financing Graduate School, 1/1/1994-12/31/1994; Series 1 (Box 4, Videocassette 24)
  - VHS Videotape - Capital Television, Inc. - GPSF - Applying to Graduate School, 1/1/1994-12/31/1994; Series 1 (Box 4, Videocassette 25)
  - VHS Videotape - Balancing the Scales Minorities and Law School (RT - 18:10), undated; Series 1 (Box 4, Videocassette 26)